# Theo McMullien

Software Developer

## **Contact Information**



Phone

+61 421 088 109



**Email** 

theomcmullien.16@gmail.com



Location

Toorak, Victoria 3142



GitHub Projects

github.com/theomcmullien

## **Technical Skills**

ASP.NET Core

RESTful API

MS SQL Server

JavaScript

HTML

CSS

React.js

Bootstrap

## References

### Anna Crooks

IT Operations & Projects Manager - ITS

- · +64 3 748 1361
- · Anna.Crooks@sit.ac.nz

#### **Anita Murphy**

Programme Manager for Undergraduate Studies - SIT

- · +64 27 841 9843
- · Anita.Murphy@sit.ac.nz

# About Me

I am a passionate and motivated Bachelor of Information Technology graduate.

My three years of studying has provided me with a strong foundation of knowledge in software development, design fundamentals, web development and advanced programming.

Achieving team awards during my study, I have proven my ability to perform well in team-oriented projects, communicating ideas, providing critical feedback and contributing to the success of the projects.

Always willing to learn and try new ideas to further develop my skills. I am eager to start my journey of continuous learning as a Software Developer.

# **Education & Qualifications**

#### O Bachelor of IT

Feb 2020 - Nov 2022

Southern Institute of Technology (SIT) - Invercargill, NZ

- Top Team Project Year 3 Information Technology Joint Award
- Top JADE Programmer Year 2 Information Technology Joint Award
- · CCNA Level 1 Certification

# Microsoft Certified: Security, Feb 2023 Compliance & Identity Fundamentals

Microsoft - Invercargill, NZ

# Work Experience

## O IT Assistant Internship

Jan 2023 - Apr 2023

Southern Institute of Technology ITS - Invercargill, NZ

- · Imaging machines and deploying software.
- · Validate licensing on deployed software.
- · Handling ticket requests.
- · Perform basic power shell scripts.
- Problem solving and bug fixing.

#### Labourer

Mar 2022 - Apr 2023

Blue Sky Pastures - Invercargill, NZ

- · Computer and scales operator.
- · General labourer.